rick Tang

Product Designer

San Francisco, California ricktang@gmail.com (315) 802-8179

Profile

UX/UI specialist focused on designing clean and functional projects across all platforms and devices in response to specific briefs and problems, while always maintaining a unique look and feel.

Uber

Product Designer

Mar 2015 - Present

- Designed safety-focused experiences for Riders and Drivers
- Physical space problem solving and it's interaction with the digital
- Navigated organization to achieve operational improvements

IFTTT

Product Designer

experience

Dec 2013 - Mar 2015

- Product and system design for a complex product
- Designed both consumer and developer products for IFTTT
- Responsible for maintaining design across iOS, Android, and web

Facebook

Product Designer

June 2013 - Sep 2013

- Designer and prototyped internal tools
- Redesigned Newsfeed curation experience for mobile
- Redesigned Newsfeed curation experience for mobile

Brown University

Education

Interdisciplinary studies, Sep 2010 - May 2013

Skills FigmaSketchPhotoshopIllustrator

Languages English: C2 | Italian: B2

CERTIFICATIONS Google UX Design Certificate